<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Synths Of Life</title>
    <link>https://mikhailspirin.github.io/synths-of-life-blog/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Synths Of Life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 23:01:45 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mikhailspirin.github.io/synths-of-life-blog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AI Synthesis Quad VCA Mixer</title>
      <link>https://mikhailspirin.github.io/synths-of-life-blog/post/aisynthesisquadvca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 23:01:45 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikhailspirin.github.io/synths-of-life-blog/post/aisynthesisquadvca/</guid>
      <description>Amazing AI Synthesis creates simple, beginner-friendly, beautiful modules and DIY kits which are thoroughly documented and well-designed. I assembled several of those some time before, and now it was time for their most complicated product - Quad VCA, which is completely smd and quite dense.
Actually it is a fix. I assebled module a year ago and didnt manage to successfully run it. Didn&amp;rsquo;t have enough experience with smd to reflow it - so it appeared in the shelf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alesis Microverb 2</title>
      <link>https://mikhailspirin.github.io/synths-of-life-blog/post/alesismicroverb2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 11:01:49 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikhailspirin.github.io/synths-of-life-blog/post/alesismicroverb2/</guid>
      <description>Had this for a while, bought without power supply. Ordered one and check - LED whorks ugly, loud crackles and hisses when moving pots, definitely worth changing it first. Allrighty, lets open it.
Visual I like the complexity colors, quality of build, everything about this board. Says 1986, assebled in Korea - and loots amazingly cool. But lets start. After some visual inspection, i also decded to change all electrolitic capacitors due to its age: fourty years straight</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strymon Aa.1 repair. First Post!</title>
      <link>https://mikhailspirin.github.io/synths-of-life-blog/post/strymon-aa1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 11:01:49 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikhailspirin.github.io/synths-of-life-blog/post/strymon-aa1/</guid>
      <description>This will be my first post. I really-really enjoy electronics. It is something magical in process of fixing and building all those electronics things. As I am a musician and long-time-obsessed-with-music-guy, this type of work is a perfect match for me. So,
Broken stuff - visual inspection One of input jacks is definitely broken. It is not regular one, so i tried to find subsittute- and yes! I found it locally.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
